vianet.com.np 2015-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Vianet Communications Pvt. Ltd.

### Privacy Policy

**We care about your Privacy**  
Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and help you understand how Vianet collects, uses and safeguards any personal information you provide to us from this Web site.

**User Registration**  
During registration a User is required to provide contact information (such as name, mailing address, telephone numbers, and email address). Vianet uses this information to maintain contact with the User as is necessary pursuant to the subscription agreement. Users must also provide billing information when subscribing to the Vianet service. This information is used for billing and payment purposes. In the event Vianet has trouble processing an order, that information is used to contact the User.

**Information Collected**  
Like most Internet sites, we do obtain some non-personally identifiable information such as the URL that referred you to our site, your Internet browser version, or type of operating system that you use. This information helps us analyze traffic patterns, perform routine maintenance, maintain site security, and is used for the solely for the purpose of improving our site navigation, measuring our advertising effectiveness and to improve the appearance of our site to the maximum number of visitors. Generally the information we collect is temporary and when you leave the site this information is deleted from our system.

Be assured that no personal information will ever be shared or sold by VIANET.

**Use of Cookies**  
VIANET sometimes uses “cookies” to enhance your experience on this web site.

Cookies cannot be used to personally identify you in any way. A cookie is a unique file that is stored on your computer. This cookie helps ensure that you don’t repeatedly see the same advertisement, such as a pop-up ad window. Although the acceptance of cookies helps us to enhance your stay at our site, they are not required to view our site.

**Sharing of Information**  
Protecting your privacy is very important to us. VIANET does not sell or share any type of personal information with anyone.

However, we can not be responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.

**Email and Spam**  
VIANET sends no unsolicited or SPAM mail, and strongly despise anyone who does. The only email we send are direct responses to our client’s database.

If you need to be removed from Internet service provider or other access provider’s mailing list you will need to contact us directly.

If you continue to receive SPAM report it to [noc@www.vianet.com.np](mailto:noc@www.vianet.com.np).

Whenever you complain about spam, it’s important to include the full email header. The information in the header makes it possible for consumer protection agencies to follow up on your complaint.

Send a copy of the spam to [noc@www.vianet.com.np](mailto:noc@www.vianet.com.np). By doing this, you can let us know about the spam problem on their system and help them to stop it in the future. Make sure to include a copy of the spam, along with the full email header. At the top of the message, state that you’re complaining about being spammed.

Most ISPs want to cut off spammers who abuse their system. Again, make sure to include a copy of the message and header information and state that you’re complaining about spam.

**Third Parties**  
Vianet’s web sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Vianet is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

Third-party resources that can be accessed with hypertext links from this web site are not under our control, and VIANET is not responsible for the contents of any of these third-party resources. The third-party links on this site are provided for your convenience only.

The inclusion of any link on this site does not imply any specific recommendation, approval or endorsement of the third party.

Please investigate any third party offers found here with their respective companies and make your own informed decisions. Review the privacy statements of each and every web site you visit to ensure your personal privacy with respect to third party offers.

The privacy information contained here pertains exclusively to the VIANET web site

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions pertaining to our privacy policy or what information we collect, and how we use such information, please feel free to contact us at 5546410 or you can email to [marketing@www.vianet.com.np](mailto:marketing@www.vianet.com.np)

**Vianet Service**  
Vianet communicates with Users via email, regular mail and telephone on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues related to User’s services.

**Policy Changes**  
Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted here. Continued use of the VIANET web site implies that you understand and agree with our privacy policy.
